# Sean O'Malley

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Achill Island, Co. Mayo

23/10/1990 087 687 85 11

<u>sean.omalley7@mail.dcu.ie</u>

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Key skills include strong results orientation, excellent team working capacity in addition to a proven commitment to delivering quality standards in all work undertaken. Over 4 years' experience working in sales and marketing and production management gives me a number of transferable skills including superb organisational, problem solving skills and the ability and experience to work under pressure with excellent communications and highly organised attitude to work.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

2014 – Present Achill Island Sea Salt

Position: Production/ Sales and Marketing Manager

Main duties:

Sales and Marketing

- Social Media and Digital Marketing
- Website Management
- Production Management
- Process Design
- Maintenance
- Funding Applications

2009 – 2014 Coláiste Acla

Position: Irish teacher for post primary students

Main duties:

- Irish Classes
- Organisation of Activities

Administration

2008-2009 Masterson's Bar and Restaurant

Position: Bar Tender/Waiter

# **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2018:

Successfully Completed MSc in Business and Information Technology at Dublin City University.

Grade: 2.1

# Sean O'Malley

## 2009 - 2013:

Successfully Completed BA Honours Degree (Irish and History) at National University of Ireland Galway.

Grade: 2.2

## **SKILLS**

- Social Media
- Business Plans
- E-commerce
- Email Marketing
- SEO
- Analytics
- CRM
- Project Management
- Web Design
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- SQL
- Multimedia
- Excel
- Powerpoint

# **REFERENCES**

Available on request